Guide to the David Peck Todd Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, PRE-1922 (1878-1922); Series I; 5 linear feet (13 boxes)
  - General Correspondence
    - Dickson, Herbert E., (5), 1911, 1913, 1915, undated (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Donald, E. Winchester, (4), 1890, 1894, 1898, undated (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Doughan, Bertha, (21), 1905-1906, [1907], [1913], n.y. October (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Doughan, James, (7), 1900, 1911-1912
    - Douglass, A. E., Lowell Observatory, Arizona, (4), 1900, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Downing, A. M. W., Royal Observatory, Greenwich, (6), 1876, 1880-1881, 1887, [1891], 1894 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Dr - Dy (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Draper, Anna Palmer (Mrs. Henry), (32), 1885, [1888], 1889-1990, [1896], 1897-1899, 1901-1902, [1905], [ca. 1906], n.y. (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Draper, Henry, (1), 1877 March 21
    - Dreyer, I. L. E., Dublin Observatory; editor, Urania, (3), 1880-1881 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Driver, Stephen William, (5), 1911-1912, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Dugan, Raymond S., (38), 1899-1905, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - E (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Edinburgh, Royal Society, (1), 1881 December 14 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Eineraud, T., Toulouse Observatory, (2), 1877 August 11, 1881 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Elkin, W. L., Yale Observatory, (4), 1888, [1894] August (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Fa - F1 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Fegunden, Franklin G., (3), 1903 October 10, 17, 25 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Field, Harriet S. (Mrs. Benjamin), (16), 1899, [1900], 1910, n.y., undated (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Fiesse, Charles, (1), 1907 August 7 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Fitch, Alice M., (3), [1883], [1885] (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Flammarion, M. Camille, Paris Observatory, (4), 1897,1913-1914 (Box 3, Folder 111)
      See also: box 115a, folder 125
    - Fletcher, William I., Amherst College Librarian, (4), 1898, 1900, 1906, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Fo - Fu (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Fossett, Perley W., machinist, (5), 1912-1913 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Frost, Edwin B., Yerkes Observatory, (5), 1905-1906, 1910, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Ga (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Gates, Merrill E., President, Amherst College, (3), 1895-1896, undated (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Ge - G1 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Georgetown College Observatory; James Curley, J. G. Hagerty, (3), 1877, 1880, 1899 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Gibbs, Edward N., (3), 1898-1899 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Gill, David, Cape of Good Hope Observatory, (7), 1880, 1889-1891, 1893, 1899, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 121)
      See also: box 2, folder 62
    - Gilman, E. H., (7), 1899, 1903, 1909-1910, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Glidden, Mr. and Mrs. Charles J., (14), 1909-1912, 1915, 1917, undated (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Go - Gu (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Goethals, George W., (8), 1907-1908, 1910-1912, 1915-1916 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Graves, J. L., (3), 1903-1904 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Graves, Louise B., (5), 1904, 1906-1907, 1911
    - Greenwich Royal Observatory
      See: box 3, folder 96
    - Grosvenor, Edwin (?) A., (6), [1891, 1892], 1893, 1895-1896, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Grubb, Sir Howard, (6), 1886, 1894-1895, 1899, undated (Box 4, Folder 128)
      See also: box 115a, folder 126
    - Guild, Curtis, Jr., (4), 1911-1912 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Ha (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Hadley, Arthur J., President, Yale University, (4), 1900, 1904, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Hale, Edward E., (4), 1894, 1898, undated (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Hale, George E., Kenwood Observatory, University of Chicago, (3), 1892, 1896, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 133)
      See also: box 115a, folder 127
    - Haliburton, R. G., (4), [ca. 1894] (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Hall, Professor Asaph, Naval Observatory, Washington, (6), 1880-1881, 1885, 1888 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Hall, G. Stanley, President, Clark University, (8), 1895, 1897-1898, 1901, 1905-1906 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Hall, Maxwell, Jamaica Observatory, (1), 1880 May 22 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Hamlin, A.D.F., Columbia School of Architecture, (4), [1895], 1903-1904 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Hammett, J. L., Company, (3), 1911 April 21, 26-27 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Hammond, Fanny Reed, (5), [1905], n.y. Jan, December (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Hammond, William Churchill, (6), [1905], [1909], 1912, undated
    - Harkness, William, Naval Observatory, Washington, D. C., (4), 1880, 1884-1885 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Harris, George, Jr., (13), 1899-1900, [1907], 1910-1911, n.y., undated (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Hartness, James, machine engineer (later Governor of Vermont), (8), 1914-1916, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Harvard College, (17), 1877-1881, 1886, 1888-1889, 1893, 1898, 1906, 1910-1911, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 144)
      See also: box 7, folder 243
    - Hazard, Caroline, President, Wellesley College, 1900, n.y. September 30 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - He (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Head, Franklin H., (4), 1897, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Head, Elizabeth, (1), 1894 April 27
    - Headley, Phineas C., (39), 1906-1916 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Headley, Margery, (1), undated
    - Hersey, Heloise E., (4), 1897-1898, undated (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Hi (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Hilder, Howard, (6), 1919-1922 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Hitchcock, E., Amherst College, (6), 1892, 1896, 1898, 1901, 1905, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Ho (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Holden, E. S., Lick Observatory, University of California, (4), 1880, 1888, 1893 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Holland, W. J., (24), 1887-1889, 1894, 1896, 1898-1899, 1901-1904, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Homfray, E. F., Gibbs and Company, Iquique, Chile, (3), 1907, 1909-1910 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Hosp, William W., Aerial Tramp, Aerial Sales Service, (8), 1920-1922, undated (Box 4, Folder 157)
      See also: box 3, folder 87
    - Hottenroth, Adolph C., (5), 1921 May, Jul, August (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Housh, G. W., Dearborn Observatory, (2), 1893 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Howe, William DeLancey, (7), 1915, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - Hu - Hy (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - Hudson, Charles J., (7), 1910, 1912-1913, undated (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - Huggins, Sir William, (9), 1885, 1888, 1890, 1894-1895, 1900 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - I (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Ingersoll, Dr. Edward P., (3), 1879, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - Ingraham, J. E., (3), 1917 Feb, Mar, June (Box 5, Folder 166)
      See also: box 4, folder 41
    - J (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - Jago, Mimi, (1), 1903 February 28 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Jago, Thomas S., (3), [ca. 1900], 1901, 1905
    - James, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur Curtis (including correspondence with W. W. Carman), (63), 1897-1900, 1902, 1905-1912, 1914-1918 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - James, Mr. and Mrs. D. Willis (including correspondence with W. W. Carman and Ellen T. Gould), (29), 1897-1899, 1902-1908, 1910, [ca. 1911], 1915-1916 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - James, William, (1), [ca. 1896] (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Japan Society, (6), 1912, 1920-1921 (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - Japanese Imperial Saké Club, (2), 1897 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - Jones, Maria Hoppin, (6), [ca. 1898-1902] (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - K (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - Keeler, James E., Allegheny Observatory, Lick Observatory, (8), [ca. 1891], 1892-1893, 1896, 1898-1900, undated (Box 5, Folder 176)
      See also: box 1, folder 6
    - Kiel, Royal Observatory, (3), 1877, 1900, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Kimball, Arthur L., (7), 1910-1911, 1917-1919 (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Knipping, E., (8), 1888-1889, 1891, [1896], 1898-1899 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Knobel, E. W., (6), 1880-1882, 1900, 1914, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - La - Le (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - Ladd, J. Wesley, (2), 1900, 1906 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - Ladd, William M., (1), 1913 August 11
    - Lailer, F. A., (2), 1913, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Lane, Rufus A., Isthmian Canal Commission, (2), 1908 March 11, 13 (Box 5, Folder 184)
      See also: box 56, folder 417
    - Langley, S. P., Smithsonian, (13), 1887-1890, 1893-1894, 1897-1898, 1906 (Box 5, Folder 185)
      See also: box 1, folder 6 See also: box 8, folder 295
    - Leipzig Library, (3), 1877, 1881 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Leonard, E. F., (4), 1899, 1906, 1910-1911 (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Leonard, W. Louise, (4), 1898, [ca. 1898], undated (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Lick Observatory, University of California, (2), 1911, [ca. 1913] (Box 5, Folder 189)
      See also: University of California, box 2, folder 56
    - Lincoln, Robert T., (5), 1909-1910, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - Li - Ly (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, (4), 1909, 1916, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - London, Royal Society, (1), 1885 January 12 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - Lord Lindsay's Observatory
      See: box 2, folder 80
    - Loud, Frank C., (10), 1878, 1893, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 194)
    - Lowell, Professor and Mrs. Percival, (46), 1895, 1897, 1899-1900, 1907, 1909-1910, 1922, undated (Box 6, Folder 195)
    - Lyman, Albert Josiah, (9), 1891, 1898, 1901, 1903-1904, 1910, undated (Box 6, Folder 196)
      See also: Albert Josiah Lyman, Photographs and Glass Plates, Todd-Bingham Picture Collection, MS 496E
    - Lynn, W.T., astronomer, (4), 1880, 1898, 1901, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 197)
    - Ma (Box 6, Folder 198)
    - Maccord, Charles W., (3), 1891, 1904-1905 (Box 6, Folder 199)
    - Maw, William H., (4), 1900 Aug, Oct, November (Box 6, Folder 200)
    - Maxim, Hiram Percy, (18), 1909-1911, 1913, 1915, 1918, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 201)
    - Mc - Me (Box 6, Folder 202)
    - Medici Society of America; Ralph T. Hale, (3), 1920-1922 (Box 6, Folder 203)
      See also: box 8, folder 289
    - Melbourne Observatory; Robert I. Ellery, (2), 1877 May 9, 28 (Box 6, Folder 204)
    - Mi - Mo (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - Milinowski, A., (2), 1906, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 206)
    - Milinowski, Marta, (5), 1909-1911
    - Mills, William H., (5), 1900-1901 (Box 6, Folder 207)
    - Mitchel Observatory, University of Cincinnati, (1), n.y. October 29 (Box 6, Folder 208)
    - Montpellier, France, Observatory; Auguste Salze, (1), undated (Box 6, Folder 209)
    - Moore, J. A., (6), 1917-1918, 1921-1922 (Box 6, Folder 210)
    - Moore, Willis L., Weather Bureau, (6), 1908, 1913, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 211)
      See also: box 9, folder 324
    - Moorehead, Warren K., (3), 1918 May, June (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - Moscow, Imperial University Observatory, (1), 1877 June 16 (Box 6, Folder 213)
    - Moulton, F. R., University of Chicago, (2), 1899 February 21, May 13 (Box 6, Folder 214)
    - Mu (Box 6, Folder 215)
    - Munroe, Mabel Stearns Noble, (2), 1906,[1906] (Box 6, Folder 216)
    - Munroe, Mary, (1), 1919 February 28
    - Murakami, H., (2), 1900, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 217)
    - N (Box 6, Folder 218)
    - New Haven geology, (2), 1916 November 3, December 1 (Box 6, Folder 219)
    - New York Botanical Garden, (2), 1901 November (Box 6, Folder 220)
    - Newberry Library, Chicago, (3), 1888, 1894 (Box 6, Folder 221)
    - Newcomb, Professor and Mrs. Simon and family, (39), 1878-1879, 1881-1882, 1886-1889, 1893-1894, 1895, 1897-1898, 1900, 1902, 1906-1909, 1916, undated (Box 6, Folder 222)
      See also: box 105, folder 31
    - Niles, Marston, (3), 1912, 1914 (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - Norton, Charles D. (and Katharine McKim Garrison Norton), (5), 1903, 1911, n.y. (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - O (Box 7, Folder 225)
    - The Observatory
      See: box 9, folder 322
    - O'Brien, Gertrude, (6), 1897, [1901], [1902], n.y., undated (Box 7, Folder 226)
    - Observatorio Astronómico Nacional Mexicano, (2), 1888 December 10 (Box 7, Folder 227)
      See also: box 9, folder 333
    - Oficina Meteorológica Argentina, (1), 1913 November (Box 7, Folder 228)
    - Okie, Mrs. Lily V. (Perley), (25), 1880-1890, 1905, undated (Box 7, Folder 229)
    - Orten, Alice S., (3), 1917, [ca. 1917] (Box 7, Folder 230)
    - Oshima, K., (4), 1897, 1899 (Box 7, Folder 231)
    - Pa (Box 7, Folder 232)
    - Palmer, Professor and Mrs. George (Alice Freeman), (12), 1897-1901, [ca. 1902] n.y., undated (Box 7, Folder 233)
    - Paris, Bureau des Longitudes, l'Observatoire de Paris, (5), 1877, 1896, 1912, undated (Box 7, Folder 234)
    - Parker, Sir Gilbert (including correspondence re: Bryce Reports), (28), 1914-1917 (Box 7, Folder 235)
    - Parkhurst, C.H., (3), 1899-1900, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 236)
    - Parsons, Charles A., (3), 1900 (Box 7, Folder 237)
    - Parsons, William Barclay, (7), 1910-1911 (Box 7, Folder 238)
    - Pe - Pl (Box 7, Folder 239)
    - Pemberton, H., Jr., (4), 1889, [1896], [1900] (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - Perkins, Julius A., (3), 1912-1913, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - Peters, E. H. F., Litchfield Observatory of Hamilton College, (5), 1876-1877, 1879-1890 (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - Pickering, Professor and Mrs. Edward C., Harvard Observatory, (57), 1877, 1880-1882, 1889, 1895, 1898, 1902, 1907, 1909-1914, 1916, 1919, undated (Box 7, Folder 243)
      See also: box 4, folder 144 See also: box 7, folder 244
    - Pickering, Professor and Mrs. W. H., Harvard Observatory, (15), 1889, 1901, 1908-1909, 1917, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 244)
    - Plecher, Andrew, (3), 1921 April 29, June 23, 24 (Box 7, Folder 245)
    - Plimpton, George A., (4), 1886, 1897, 1901, 1907 (Box 7, Folder 246)
    - Po - Pu (Box 7, Folder 247)
    - Pope, Colonel Albert A., (8), 1897, 1899-1902 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - Porter, R. W., (2), 1918, undated (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - Prague Observatory, (1), 1877 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - Pratt, George D., (4), 1903-1904, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - Pritchett, Henry S., Washington University Observatory, Coast and Geodetic Survey, (7), 1889, 1899, 1904, 1906, 1908 (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - Proctor, Mary, (6), 1897, 1902-1903, 1906 (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - Pujazon, D. Cecilio, San Fernando, Spain, Observatory, (2), 1877 April 13, 1891 April 15 (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - Purrington, William A., (6), 1909, 1920-1921, n.y., undated (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - Ra - Re (Box 8, Folder 256)
    - Reeves, Tom, (10), 1876-1877 (Box 8, Folder 257)
      See also: box 105, folder 34
    - Rh - Ri (Box 8, Folder 258)
    - Rice, Mrs. Ellen F., (14), [1902], 1904-1906, undated (Box 8, Folder 259)
    - Riley, William F., (8), 1902, 1904, 1909, 1910, 1914, 1918, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 260)
    - Ritchey, G. W., (1), 1912 January 20 (Box 8, Folder 261)
    - Ro - Ru (Box 8, Folder 262)
    - Robinson, Mr. and Mrs. Edward (Elizabeth), (13), 1892, [1900], 1904, undated (Box 8, Folder 263)
    - Robinson, H. M., (6), 1906, [1907], 1908, 1910 (Box 8, Folder 264)
    - Rockwell, C. R., (13), 1905-1906, [ca. 1907], 1915 (Box 8, Folder 265)
    - Rockwell, John (re: almucantar), (2), 1905 January 24, February 16
    - Rogers, Henry M., (4), 1907, 1910-1911, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 266)
    - Rotch, Abbott Lawrence, Blue Hills Meteorological Observatory, (19), [ca. 1895], 1896-1897, [ca. 1900], 1901-1903, 1905-1906, 1909-1910, 1912, n.y. (Box 8, Folder 267)
    - Royal Astronomical Society, London, (2), 1881 December 13, 1926 November 22 (Box 8, Folder 268)
    - Sa - Sc (Box 8, Folder 269)
      See also: Photographs and Glass Plates, Series VII, "Aloha": photographs of launching of "Aloha" by Herbert L. Sattula
    - Safford, T. H., Williams College, (7), 1876-1879, 1882 (Box 8, Folder 270)
    - St. Petersburg, Imperial Academy of Science, (1), 1914 (Box 8, Folder 271)
    - St. Petersburg, Imperial University, S. Glosenopp, Director, (3), 1880, 1882 (Box 8, Folder 272)
    - Saito, Kuniji, Tokyo Observatory (re: David Peck Todd's work in Japan observing solar eclipses in 1887 and 1896), (7), 1968 September 26 - November 6 (Box 8, Folder 273)
    - Sawyer, Philip, (3), 1898-1899, n.y. (Box 8, Folder 274)
    - Schiff, Jacob H., and family, (28), 1892-1894, 1899-1900, 1905, 1908-1912, 1914-1915, 1917, [1922], [1926], n.y., undated (Box 8, Folder 275)
    - Schiff, Mortimer, (5), 1912, 1915, undated
    - Schlesinger, Frank, Allegheny Observatory, (2), 1906 October 29, December 7 (Box 8, Folder 276)
    - Schuster, Arthur (England), (2), 1881-1882 (Box 8, Folder 277)
    - Science, (33), 1883-1886, 1899, 1920, undated (Box 8, Folder 278)
      See also: box 8, folder 280
    - Scientific American, J. Bernard Walker, (4), 1902, 1925, 1927, n.y. (Box 8, Folder 279)
    - Scudder, Samuel H., (3), 1886-1887, 1890 (Box 8, Folder 280)
      See also: box 8, folder 278
    - Se - Sh (Box 8, Folder 281)
    - Searles, Edward F., (17), [1902], 1903-1905, 1910, 1915-1916, n.y. (Box 8, Folder 282)
    - See, Professor T. J. J., United States Naval Observatory, (2), 1899 May 7, 1910 December 1 (Box 8, Folder 283)
      See also: box 116, folder 138
    - Seelye, Professor Julius, (2), 1877 March 13, April 30 (Box 8, Folder 284)
    - Seelye, L. Clark, (3), 1886-1887, 1898 (Box 8, Folder 285)
      See also: box 8, folder 288
    - Serviss, Garrett P.
      See: box 71, folder 31
    - Shanklin, William Arnold, (4), 1910, 1913, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 286)
    - Shaw, Frank D., (3), 1911, 1920, undated (Box 8, Folder 287)
    - Si - Sn (Box 8, Folder 288)
    - Small, Maynard and Company, Inc; Ralph T. Hale, (3), 1908, 1910-1911, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 289)
      See also: box 6, folder 203
    - Smith, Charles Sprague, (3), 1889, 1899 (Box 8, Folder 290)
    - Smith, Edward A., (3), 1918 September 21, 26, October 3 (Box 8, Folder 291)
    - Smith, Henry Kirk, (2), [1910], 1911 May 28 (Box 8, Folder 292)
    - Smith, Mr. and Mrs. Henry Preserved, (5), 1899-1900, 1908, n.y., undated (Box 8, Folder 293)
    - Smith, Mary Chapin, (8), [1910-1911], [ca. 1913], 1915, n.y. (Box 8, Folder 294)
    - Smithsonian Institution, (4), 1876, 1878-1879, 1887 (Box 8, Folder 295)
      See also: box 5, folder 185
    - So - Sp (Box 9, Folder 296)
    - Springfield Republican, Samuel Bowles, (5), 1892, 1902, 1913, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 297)
    - Sprague, Jennie B., (1), 1910 May 9 (Box 9, Folder 298)
    - St (Box 9, Folder 299)
    - Starr, Frederick, University of Chicago, (2), 1913 February 22, December 12 (Box 9, Folder 300)
    - Stearns, Alfred E., (2), 1903 February 5, 1906 July 8 (Box 9, Folder 301)
    - Stearns, Mrs. William F. (mother), (2), [ca. 1890's], [1899]
    - Stockwell, J. N., (2), 1876 May 26, 1877 August 8 (Box 9, Folder 302)
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps, (4), 1908 January-February (Box 9, Folder 303)
    - Stone, Mrs. C. E. Whiton, (4), 1903 May-June (Box 9, Folder 304)
    - Stone, Enrique, (3), 1908-1909 (Box 9, Folder 305)
    - Stone, Ormond, (2), 1877, [1880] (Box 9, Folder 306)
    - Strong, Edward A., (9), 1902, 1904-1907, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 307)
    - Strong, M. E., (4), 1899, 1904, undated
    - Strong, Marion H. (Mrs. Edward A.?), (1), n.y. January 30
    - Sw - Sy (Box 9, Folder 308)
    - Swift, Dr. Lewis, (8), [ca. 1875], 1880, 1896, 1903, undated (Box 9, Folder 309)
      See also: box 12, folder 391 See also: box 9, folder 309
    - Sydney Observatory; H. A. Russell, (3), 1877, 1880, undated (Box 9, Folder 310)
    - Sykes, C. W., (3), 1909, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 311)
    - Sylvester, I. I., (4), 1876-1877, 1883, 1885 (Box 9, Folder 312)
    - Ta - Te (Box 9, Folder 313)
    - Taft, William H., (3), 1910, 1912, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 314)
    - Th - Ti (Box 9, Folder 315)
    - Thaw, E. D., (2), undated (Box 9, Folder 316)
    - Thaw, M. E. (Mrs. William), (2), 1901, [ca. 1902]
    - Thomson, Elihu, (12), 1900, [1901], 1907, 1909, 1911, 1914, 1918, undated (Box 9, Folder 317)
    - To (Box 9, Folder 318)
    - Touillart, C., Lille, (3), 1878, 1880-1881 (Box 9, Folder 319)
    - Tr - Ty (Box 9, Folder 320)
    - Tucker, H. G., (3), 1899, [ca. 1899], undated (Box 9, Folder 321)
    - Turner, H. H., The Observatory, (8), [ca. 1880], 1888-1889, 1892, 1899-1900 (Box 9, Folder 322)
      See also: box 116, folder 139
    - U (Box 9, Folder 323)
    - United States Department of Agriculture, Weather Bureau, (9), [ca. 1880], [ca. 1881], 1898-1899, 1908, 1911-1912, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 324)
      See also: box 6, folder 211
    - United States Department of the Interior, Bureau of Education, (1), 1898 January 20 (Box 9, Folder 325)
    - United States Library of Congress, (2), 1880 April 2, 1881 May 21 (Box 9, Folder 326)
    - United States Naval Observatory, (5), 1875, [ca. 1880], 1881, 1889, 1899 (Box 9, Folder 327)
    - United States Navy Department, (7), 1877-1878, 1890, 1899-1900, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 328)
    - United States State Department, (2), 1881 February 10, June 11 (Box 9, Folder 329)
    - United States War Department, Chief of Engineers, Chief Signal Officer, (7), 1877-1880, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 330)
    - Upsala, Observatoire Astronomique Royal, (2), 1881 April 19, July 18 (Box 9, Folder 331)
    - V (Box 9, Folder 332)
    - Valle, Felipe, Mexican National Observatory, (3), 1881, 1896-1897 (Box 9, Folder 333)
      See also: box 7, folder 227
    - Van Arsdale, G. D., (2), 1911 September 8, 1917 January 24 (Box 9, Folder 334)
    - W (Box 9, Folder 335)
    - Walker, Williston, (4), 1899, 1901, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 336)
    - Ward, Henry A., (5), 1902, 1904-1905, 1908 (Box 9, Folder 337)
    - Ward, Henry C.(?), (3), 1911, undated (Box 9, Folder 338)
    - Ward, Herbert D., (3), 1899-1900 (Box 9, Folder 339)
    - Warner, Worcester R., Warner and Swasey, (11), 1887, 1898, 1909-1910, 1912, 1920-1921, undated (Box 9, Folder 340)
    - We (Box 10, Folder 341)
    - Webb, Mr. and Mrs. James C. (Nellie S.), (6), 1904, 1906, 1910 (Box 10, Folder 342)
    - Welles, F. R., (4), 1909, 1912, 1915 (Box 10, Folder 343)
      See also: box 10, folder 343
    - Welles, Robert (son), (3), 1911-1912 (Box 10, Folder 343)
      See also: box 116, folder 141
    - Wh - Wi (Box 10, Folder 344)
    - Wheeler, Penelope, (3), 1916 March 11, 16-17 (Box 10, Folder 345)
    - Whitcomb, G. Henry, (1), 1898 (Box 10, Folder 346)
    - Whitcomb, Henry E., (4), 1899, 1904 (Box 10, Folder 346)
    - Whitin, Sarah E., (12), 1898-1901 (Box 10, Folder 347)
    - Whiting, Lilian, (2), 1897 April 29, May 14 (Box 10, Folder 348)
    - Whiting, Sarah F., (6), 1900, 1903, 1905, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 348)
    - Wien University; E. Weiss, Director, (3), 1877, 1880-1881 (Box 10, Folder 349)
    - Williams, Talcott, (4), 1898, 1900, 1906 (Box 10, Folder 350)
    - Wilmarth, Matilda R., (3), 1890, 1902, 1905 (Box 10, Folder 351)
    - Winslow, Helen M., (4), 1902, 1910, n.y. (Box 10, Folder 352)
    - Wo (Box 10, Folder 353)
    - Wood, Leonard, (4), 1916, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 354)
    - Woolley, Mary E., Mount Holyoke, (12), 1902, 1904-1905, 1911-1912, 1914, n.y. (Box 10, Folder 355)
      See also: box 10, folder 361
    - Wr - Wy (Box 10, Folder 356)
    - Wright, Arthur W., Yale, (5), 1881, 1901, 1904 (Box 10, Folder 357)
    - Y - Z (Box 10, Folder 358)
    - Yale College Observatory, (1), 1883 March 30 (Box 10, Folder 359)
      See also: box 8, folder 276
    - Yerkes Observatory, University of Chicago, (4), 1897, 1909, 1914, undated (Box 10, Folder 360)
    - Young, Anne Sewell, Mount Holyoke, (7), [ca. 1905], 1908, 1911, 1913, 1915, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 361)
      See also: box 10, folder 355
    - Young, C. A., Princeton Observatory, (17), 1880-1881, 1886, 1888, 1893-1894, 1896, 1898-1899, 1904, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 362)
      See also: box 116, folder 142
    - Observatories and Astronomers, various letters re: publications of David Peck Todd (Box 10, Folder 363)
    - Unidentified Correspondent (two series of letters from same correspondent; including letter of explanation by Millicent Todd Bingham to Dr. Ehrenelon (ca. 69), 1909 May 5 - July 8, 1913 July 5 - 1914 April 27 (Box 10, Folder 364)
      See also: box 12, folder 391
    - Unidentified (Box 10, Folder 365)
  - Family Correspondence
    - Avery, Susan Look (MLT's relative on her father's side), (1), 1891 September 24 (Box 11, Folder 366)